So you'll leave?
Yes.
I'm almost completely healed.
Laojun's medicine helped.
I'm a bit torn.
I'm glad you've recovered,
but we'll miss you.
I'll visit you guys often.
You haven't told Xiaobai yet, have you?
No.
How much time do you need?
I should be ready by tomorrow.
Can you take a human form?
Yes.
Wow, can I see it?
It's awkward to transform in front of you.
I understand.
So you leave tomorrow?
Why not rest a bit more?
I'd rather finish the quest.
I'll visit you after that.
Okay.
Go on, say goodbye to Xiaobai.
Sure.
Before I forget.
Can you lend me some clothes?
I reverted to my base state.
My clothes didn't survive.
Sure, I can.
Early today morning, an aircraft of
MT Airlines crashed in Longyou City.
The passengers were discovered on roofs of houses near the site.
The Lawful and Lawless
The cause of the baffling phenomenon is under investigation.
We interviewed a fortunate survivor.
I don't care what it was.
From this day on,
I believe in God's existence.
I thank him for saving me.
I will cherish my life even more.
It must have been a spirit.
Incidents involving spirits are
on the news 10-20 times a year.
So many?
So few, actually.
Many spirits live secluded.
Those who live among humans, must hide their identities.
Aside from incidents like this,
most of them never get exposed.
The club hall prohibits flying over the city.
He'll be punished.
How do you know their rules so well?
I used to live there.
I see.
So every spirit lives in hiding?
Not at all.
A lot of them make good use of their abilities in the human world.
Some are even rich and famous.
How do you know that?
Spirit boards, tabloid section.
Oh...
What?
I'm gonna sunbathe.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I can tell her then.
I'm leaving soon.
Always listen to Xiaobai.
If you don't behave, they won't keep you.
Good morning, boss!
Good morning.
I think I heard ex-boss.
Is he on a trip?
He's having fun.
I'll go check it out.
Boss!!
Silence.
Boss!
A lot of our comrades have disappeared.
What if it's...?
Leave it to me.
Daddy!
Hello, dear! Had breakfast yet?
Who'll be at the door first?
Me, me, me!
Boss!
They're empty!
How did they escape?
Stop!
A cat spirit?
Kid!
What do you want?
Let him go.
Why exactly?
All right.
I can do that much for you.
It's rare I meet someone of my kind.
But tell me, little fellow,
why do you want to save a human like this?
Spirits, humans, animals.
Whose side are you on?
None of your business.
Stop kidnapping humans!
Do you know the local club hall?
Yes.
I've got special permission from them.
In other words, I'm a lawful hunter.
What?
But I have no intention to become your enemy about such a thing.
I'll try to avoid you.
Let's not meet again, kitten!
Daddy!
Daddy, are you all right? Daddy!
Xiaohei.
What are you doing up there?
Sunbathing?
Let's hang the clothes.
Howdy, Xiaohei!
Enjoying sunshine?
I've got some of the good stuff.
Have you ever tasted the flavor of life?
Take a sip.
What's This Taste?
Xiaohei?
What do you think, what's wrong with Xiaohei?
Seemingly there's nothing wrong.
He's got a fever.
It can't be.
Spirits don't catch human illnesses.
Also, a cat's body is warmer than a human's.
I see...
Hello? Shanxin?
No, don't come over!
Just one question.
Maybe he yearns for a girl.
What?
Do you want me to lend you Huang?
Oh, shut up...
You should take him to a vet.
Okay, thanks.
Can we take him to a vet?
Absolutely not.
Also, it wouldn't help.
I thought so.
Xiaohei!
It's like he's drunk...
Gen, come quick!
They're just Heixius.
What on earth..?
Now he's sound asleep.
Maybe he's just tired?
What do we do now?
Have a cup!
Don't worry, he'll be all right.
No!!
This is not good...
Stay here for a while.
Xiaohei, you're up?
What's that smell?
Let them go.
I will once you feel better.
Now get some rest.
You wanna fight?
Stop it!
He really got stronger...
What am I doing here?
What happened?
Feeling better?
I'll release the Heixius then.
Just now...
Again?!
Stop it!
Yoohoo, I'm home!
What happened here?!
Grandpa...
It won't
happen again
Xiaohei?
Xiaobai.
I must leave now.
You really have to leave now?
Yeah...
Did I scare you?
I knew it was you the moment I saw you.
So you can transform into a human form!
I've never thought you could.
I'm not very good at it yet.
How come your hair is white?
Oh, yeah, my hair.
It used to be black.
So, you really are older than Grandpa?
No, no. I'm 10 years old too.
When's your birthday?
Around November 1st.
Younger than me. You could be my little brother.
"Around"?
I don't know when I was born.
My master picked a day for me.
You're returning to him then?
No, first I have to finish a quest.
So you will come back sometime?
Of course. I'll introduce you to Master later.
He's the best person in the whole world!
Visit as soon as you can!
Xiaohei!
Xiaohei?
Xiaohei already left.
You knew that he was going to leave?
Yes.
He only wanted to stay while he recovered.
I miss Dad and Mom a little...
They'd be happy to hear this.
Hi, Xiaobai!!
Long time no see
We are fine
We're on
a rollercoaster
Please don't
call now
What??
I can't hear you!!
Parting and Reunion
Grandpa, I'm going swimming!
Okay.
Bidiu, come!
I'll be back as soon as I can!!
What?
Manager!
Oh, Mr. Xiaohei.
Can I use the hall's teleport system?
Sure. Where do you need to go?
To Longyou.
Setting out for your next quest?
You know about it?
Yes. But you don't have to go to Longyou.
Why?
Hey, kitten!
How you're doing?
How do you know it's me?
You've never seen my human form.
I've been watching you for a while.
And of course that little girl.
What did you say?
Don't take it the wrong way!
She can't be in the scope of my hunting permit.
I just came to travel.
I'll go up by myself, Manager.
Okay.
You permit humans getting hunted?
He's special.
His name is Niepa.
He's a man-eater.
Man-eater?
Yes.
Even we can't prohibit their kind from hunting.
We can only restrict their permits to "evil people".
Those who they hunt down must be brought here so we can examine them.
Can't they just eat other food?
No. They're like blood eaters.
They can only get nutrition from a specific food.
All we can do is to inform them about people on death row and vicious criminals.
And conversely:
if they are hunted down by humans,
we don't intervene.
Can you... really do this?
What else could we do?
We can't deprive them of their right to live.
Ultimately,
they are victims as well.
Not only humans,
but most spirits also loathe them.
But they simply have no choice.
So you guys just let them hunt humans?
What other choice is there?
Do we provide their food?
Or raise it, the same way humans do?
A few days ago, I met Wuxian in Longyou.
He's in Longyou?
No, he already left.
He asked me to give you your next quest.
Thank you.
Manager.
Please read it for me.
Don't forget! Servers start tomorrow at 10.
We can't be late!
I know, you already told me a thousand times.
It's gonna revolutionize gaming.
I guarantee you'll be hooked on it once you played!
Okay, okay, I'll be there on time.
Don't you forget it!
I won't.
Bye!
Bye, bye!
She just can't stop talking when it comes to games.
Sometimes I don't see Shanxin for days.
How come I don't miss her?
Because you know where to find her.
You're right.
What do you think, when will Xiaohei return?
He only left a day ago.
One day...
What if he's back right away?
I'm back.
Huh?!
Xiaohei!!
What goodbye lasts less than one episode?
Now you're talking like Grandpa.
Have you finished your quest?
Not yet.
I'm here because of it.
Huh?
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Our destination may be whimsical
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
kore kara deau kimi e to
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Mochiyotta hako aketara
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
Are so precious and so fleeting
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Those feelings will never fade away
Omoi wa kitto kienai
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me
Kitto boku wo yonderu